# **Kushkumar Patel**

+1 (647) 904 9277 | kushpatel2203@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/kushpatel22

# **Summary**

An experienced QA Analyst with a strong technical background and knowledge of software testing principles and processes. Skillfully leads software projects, develops test strategies, and performs thorough testing to ensure product quality and reliability. Possesses excellent problem-solving skills, an analytical mind, and the ability to multi-task in a fast-paced environment.

# **Work Experience**

# Technical Support Consultant Rogers Communications Inc. – Remote

(April 2022 – Present)

- Connect with clients resolving a wide range of technical issues related to hardware, software, and network connectivity.
- Work with cable and key telecom technologies like IOT, DOCSIS, GPON and other web services.
- Troubleshoot and resolved issues related to operating systems, including Windows and macOS, as well as hardware components, such as printers, routers, and modems.
- Utilized a ticketing system to manage customer inquiries, ensuring prompt resolution and timely follow-up.
- Worked with four different teams according to devices in which the issue is
- Troubleshooting IMAP, POP3 and SMTP settings for the clients in email setup and work with connectivity issues in Microsoft Outlook.

#### **QA Analyst**

### Samskrita Bharati – Brampton

(August 2021 – December 2021)

- Designed and executed manual and automated tests, using tools such as Selenium and JIRA, to verify the functionality and performance of applications.
- Worked closely with two developers and project manager to identify and resolve issues, ensuring that applications were delivered on time and met high-quality standards.
- Participated in regular code reviews and provided constructive feedback to improve software quality and reduce the number of defects.
- Contributed to continuous improvement of testing processes and procedures, resulting in increased efficiency and improved test coverage.
- Meeting with college students to provide remote side technical support for software installation and troubleshooting other network connectivity problems.
- Escalated relevant high-level support tickets and incidents to the appropriate teams.

# **Kushkumar Patel**

+1 (647) 904 9277 | kushpatel2203@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/kushpatel22

# COVID Screener/ Service Representative (Part-time) Paladin Security

(January 2021 – present)

- Developed interactive skills by dealing with different people's problems and providing them with every service they need.
- Adapted to varying team dynamics, which contributed to the development of a collaborative team environment.
- Developed other soft skills like teamwork and organization skills, problem-solving and critical thinking, professionalism, and strong work ethics.

### **Technical Skills**

- **Software**: MS Office Applications, HP Quality Center, TestRail, VirtualBox, VMWare, JIRA, Bugzilla, Slack and Microsoft Teams.
- Languages/Frameworks: Java, JavaScript, C/C++, Python, Selenium, Appium
- Development and Database: MVC, GIT, GitHub, Visual Studio, Eclipse, SDLC, Agile, MySQL, MongoDB, MS SQL

## **Education**

### **Software Development and Network Engineering**

(Jan 2020 - Dec 2022)

Sheridan Institute of Technology and Advanced Learning GPA: 3.7 / 4.0

## **Related Projects**

### LetMeBook (Clinic Appointment System) (GitHub)

- This application helps customer to book an appointment to visit a specific doctor at a particular clinic
- Made with React for front-end, .NET for back-end and Firebase for database management system. Bootstrap framework used for some designing of website.
- This project was done by group of 4 people as a Capstone project
- I have also did the API testing using Postman and automated testing of some funtions using Selenium

#### MyDailymotion Website (C#, .Net, WebAPI, Angular, UI/UX, HTTPS) (GitHub)

- This Software is the clone of video and news publishing website, but with different interface.
- This is fully functional website with all working searched videos and news.